Legionaries You are a volunteer serving
France with honor and fidelity.
You respect defeated enemies.
You never abandon your dead, your wounded,
or your arms.
Respect for traditions, devotion to your
leaders, discipline and comradeship are
your strengths, courage, and loyalty your
virtues.
It's your Legionary State.
Some of the participants pretended to
recite their text.
The warrant officer stops them all at
once.
Some people are fishes.
Nothing escapes the dreaded adjutant.
You're being a fish.
Don't you know your text?
Why?
Bomb the torso.
Those who speak little have little to
answer.
Is that it?
It doesn't work like that.
Okay, Master Corporal, they're going to
join the local pikes.
All right, let's go.
To the Legion, for every mistake comes its
punishment.
Here, the penalty is a sprint around the
building.
Not good, not good.
We're going to refresh their will.
A sprint, it helps their will to learn.
That's not good now.
Rally, rally.
Once the legionaries are back in line, the
adjutant gives them a second chance.
You're yelling too much.
Or talking too fast.
It's not pretty.
I know you're hungry.
You want to get to the table quickly.
But you don't get to decide.
We quote the code of honor from the heart.
We don't shout.
And we recite calmly.
Respectful of traditions.
Attached to your leaders, discipline and
fellowship are your strength.
Rest.
We are good.
But not very well yet.